I think grandma already knew about us
even earlier than I did.
It's like I was destined to be with you.
Grandma saw the destined fate earlier.
You think Grandma’s lived her life blind?
When Grandma found out about homosexuality
your mom wasn't even born yet.
Hey.
You call it quite naturally.
Mom asked me to.
Have you helped grandma a lot
in the past two years?
She’s known it all along.
Junjun, you don't miss my grandson
or my second grandson.
I sent her a WeChat message last night.
Saying I would come back for dinner tonight.
Qingtian isn't here.
Then who do you think it could be?
You're so smart.
Aren't you afraid of grandma's objection?
If she objects
I'll bring up how she sends gifts and money
to cute male streamers.
It will be a hot search.
A generation of beautiful stars and sunny grandmothers
#CuteMaleStreamerJohnDoeGetsBigTips
Trending topics aren't not that long.
How about this then...
#SupportElderlyEntertainment
Just some fun for the elderly.